STACK

- React JS
- Tailwind CSS
- Javascript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Redux JS
- Node JS

I am a programmer with strong soft skills, excelling in communication, teamwork, adaptability to changes, leadership, self-learning, and more. I have a solid experience in HTML5. CSS3. JavaScript. Tailwind, and ReactJS, specializing in front-end web development and creating high performance interactive interfaces

CONTACT



<u>Portfolio</u>



+57 3212159041



edwar.leon.m@gmail.com



<u>LinkedIn</u>

SOFT SKILLS

Leadership

Communication

Adaptability to changes

Self-learning

Teamwork

LANGUAGES

English B1

Native Spanish

LEÓN EDWAR

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

MAY 2023 - PRESENT

Full Stack Web Developer - Academio

Outstanding student in the fundamentals and React JS modules, creating projects with solid foundations in full stacks. Link here.

APRIL 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022

WEB DEVELOPER - Alura (ONE)

Link here.

EXPERIENCE

APRIL 2022 - FEBRUARY 2023 Atlantic QI

CALL CENTER SUPERVISOR

Led a team of 40 managers to achieve metrics compliance for IBM Spain and ensure account payroll. Increased management quality from 45% to 87% within the first 2 months and enhanced agent productivity from 45 records to 60.

AUGUST 2015 - DECEMBER 2021 Innovacryl - LD

ADMINISTRATOR

Strategically planned and directed operations. Analyzed and optimized financial resources and processes. Achieved a 20% increase in sales and a 43% boost in product production in the first year.

PROJECTS

POKEDEX

- Web application for searching Pokémon and accessing their abilities and statistics.
- This project utilized React Js, Tailwind, Redux Js, Git, and API consumption.
- Repository link, Project link

RICK AND MORTY APP

- Web application for searching characters from the series and learning about their origin and status.
- This project employed React Js, Tailwind, Redux Js, Git, and API consumption.
- · Repository link, Project link

- Web application for user creation, updating, and deletion.
- This project utilized React Js, Tailwind, React form, Git, and API consumption.
- Repository link, Project link